kboards.com 2017-07-02

# Kboards Privacy Policy

## Commitment to Privacy

KBoards is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected while you're here at the KBoards website. 

## Email Addresses

You provide your email address when you register in our forums. That email address is used to confirm your registration, and to receive alerts regarding Personal Messages (PMs) sent to you through our PM system, and any thread updates that you choose to be notified with through the NOTIFY button at the top of each thread. 

By default, your email address is hidden from all forum members except our moderators. If you wish it to be viewable in the forums, you will have to go your forum Profile Page and adjust the Hide Email Address setting. 

**We have never sold or given away the email addresses of our members, and never will.**

## Log Files

Like most standard websites, this website uses log files. These include: Internet Protocol addresses (IP addresses), browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, and date/time stamp. **This information is not linked to personally identifiable information.**

## Web Cookies

Our forum software does use cookies. Web cookies (also known as HTTP cookies, or just cookies) are parcels of text that are sent by a server to a Web browser, and then sent back unchanged by the browser each time it accesses that server. In other words, a cookie is a piece of data stored on a user's computer that is tied to information about the user.

**If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options.** Please check your browser's help section for instructions on how to do this. Note that if you do this, your login session will not be retained and you may have to re-log in each time you visit the site.

## Links

This website contains links to other websites. Some links are provided by us and some are provided by forum members in their posts. **Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of other websites.** We encourage you, when you leave this website, to read the privacy policy (or privacy statement) of each website you visit. This privacy policy applies solely to this particular website.

## Advertisers and Analytics

Our advertising partners include, but are not limited to, Google Adsense and Amazon.com. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or web beacons) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see. We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads and collect information when users visit our site. These companies may use information about users' visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements on our site, other websites, and other forms of media about goods and services of interest to such users. **To protect your privacy, this information is limited to non-personally-identifiable information.**

Our analytics services include Google Analytics and Statcounter. These services may also use technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or web beacons) to collect analytics data about web traffic to our site. **This information is limited to non-personally-identifiable information.**

KBoards has no access to or control over third-party advertisers. You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt out of certain practices. **KBoards's privacy policy does not apply to, and cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.**

## Webmaster Contact Information

If you have any questions or suggestions regarding the KBoards privacy policy, please feel free to contact us at [admin@www.kboards.com](mailto:admin@www.kboards.com).
